I'm looking for the right girl to be princess, the right girl for these glass slipper.
Prince, I'm the only one who can do it.
Make a pact with me. Make a pact with me.
Please make a contract with me
K.A.R.I K.A.R.I together
K.A.R.I., K.A.R.I., K.A.R.I.
K.A.R.I For the first time, K.A.R.I not let you sa
This was my first time experiencing 360 Reality Audio.
The feeling of having the entire space filled with music...
The feeling of being able to reach places that are normally out of reach
It was a strange and slightly ticklish sensation at first.
I enjoyed hearing the 10 unique voices from all sides of the room.
I also enjoy panning or creating space when I write and mix a song.
I also feel the joy of panning or creating a space when I write and mix a song.
I feel the joy of panning or creating space when I'm making a song and mixing it.
This time, I was able to see and feel where the sound was coming from, as if I had drawn a picture of it with my own eyes.
After listening to the headphones through the speakers, I put on the headphones.
I really didn't feel like I was wearing headphones.
I didn't even feel like I was wearing them.
I didn't feel like I was wearing headphones at all.
I could listen to the same kind of music with only one pair of headphones
It was amazing to be able to listen to the same kind of music with just one pair of headphones.
There were 10 of us, and we had to do a lot of dialogues.
It was as if we were actually moving in formation.
It was like we were actually moving through the formation.
I thought it was really fun.
I thought it would be really fun to hear the sound
I thought it would be really fun to hear the sound.
I'd like to see a live performance of "Sekusu" with a trolley going around the venue in a 180 degree turn.
I was on a trolley that spun 180 degrees around the venue, and I felt as if I could actually feel the members of the trolley spinning around.
I thought I could experience that feeling at home or anywhere, like actually hearing the applause of the fans.
I thought it would be really interesting to hear the sound of the fans clapping, and to have a three-dimensional experience of a real live concert.
I thought that was really interesting.
I was able to listen to "JUMP".
The chorus was so powerful.
When there are 10 members in a group, you can hear the individual voices of each one of them.
I think it's fun to listen to them because you can hear each person's unique voice.
I think it's fun to listen to them.
In a group, the chorus is often sung in unison.
I think it's hard to hear who is singing and what nuance they are singing when you listen to the song with poor sound.
I think it's hard to hear who is singing and what nuance they are singing.
But if I use this speaker or this environment, I can hear the nuances of the song.
I can feel the nuance of what this girl is listening to.
If I move, I can feel it.